http://www.sparxsystems.com.au/privacy.html

Pro Cloud Server
What is new in v4.2What was new in v4.1What was new in v4 Overview
Privacy Policy
At Sparx Systems Pty Ltd (Australian Business Number: 38 085 034 546) (defined here as 'We' or 'Our'),
We value your comments, suggestions and feedback. Our Privacy Policy sets out how we collect,
use and disclose "personal information" and other "non-personal information" we have gathered
about you about you in relation to our software products Enterprise Architect" (all versions)
All MDG Integrations, MDG Technologies and MDG Links", and the Pro Cloud Server (all versions)
including WebEA, ("Software" which term includes the associated Website).
By using our Software, you acknowledge and consent to the terms of this privacy policy.
This policy will let you know:
What information (often referred to as 'data') is collected from you;
How your information is used;
With whom your information may be shared;
How you can access, update, or delete your information.
We will comply with all relevant and applicable legislative requirements, and, in the event
of any inconsistency, the legislative requirements will override the provisions of this document.
What data do we collect?
We collect data in the following ways:
Data collected automatically; and
Data you provide us directly.
Data collected automatically
Our Software does not collect any data automatically. However, the website for the Software does
use Google Analytics which may collect certain non-personal data.
Details of that third-party service can be found below under 'Collection of Non-Personal Information' below.
Data you provide us
We collect and store your email when you sign up for our Software. We will also keep your contact details
if you contact us for a particular purpose.
What is Personal Information?
'Personal Information' is information that identifies you as an individual.
We do not collect this type of information unless you submit it to us directly.
If you contact us with a comment or query, We keep a copy of any personal information you provide.
This is so that we can respond to your comments and questions as a part of our commitment to
providing you with player support. If you contact us directly for any reason, we also keep
a copy of that correspondence.
What is Sensitive Information?
Sensitive information includes information about such things as an individual's racial or
ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious or
philosophical beliefs, membership of a professional body, criminal records or health information.
We will not attempt to obtain nor record any sensitive information.
Collection of other 'Non-Personal' Information
Non-personal information is general, non-identifiable and anonymous information that is gathered
for statistical, analytical and research purposes. Some non-personal information may be gathered
while you use Our Software's website (found at https://www.sparxsystems.com).
Though we do not use cookies in order to track your movement around the web, Our website uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use these sites. The tool uses cookies to collect Internet log information and general visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website, including your IP address, is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate use of our website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
The Google Analytics privacy policy can be found here:
Google Analytics: https://policies.google.com/privacy
Access to your data, and permanent deletion of your data
We will retain your data only as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as to comply
with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
No matter how we come in contact with your data, you have the right to access the data We hold
about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions.
Data Subject Requests
In the event that you send a data subject request to Us, We will respond to that request in
accordance with any applicable legislation.
If you wish to know what data we hold about you, if any, please make out your request to us in
writing at the address listed below. Please be aware that in order to protect the information
in Our database, We will require identification from you before releasing any information.
Disclosure, and Security of Your Information
We will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any of the personal information you provide to us for any reason, without your prior consent. Otherwise, your Personal Information will only be disclosed where required or allowable by law.
Your Personal Information is stored offsite in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.
Policy Updates
This Policy may change from time to time. The most current version of our Privacy Policy can be found at https://sparxsystems.com/privacy.html We will always keep this up to date so that you know what information we will collect from you, how we may use it, and when we may disclose it.
Complaints
You can lodge a complaint with us about any breach of our Privacy Policy at the address below.
Privacy Policy Contact Information
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
© 2000 - 2020   Sparx Systems Pty Ltd.   All rights Reserved.
Legal
Privacy
About us
